{
    "subject": "resource/Zen\u00f3n_Franco_Ocampos",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Paraguay",
    "human_readable": "Zen\u00f3n Franco Ocampos was born in Paraguay.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8880288004875183,
            "question": "Where was Zen\u00f3n Franco Ocampos born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7282763719558716,
            "question": "What nationality is Zen\u00f3n Franco Ocampos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7159456014633179,
            "question": "Who else was born in Paraguay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5982658863067627,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Zen\u00f3n Franco Ocampos' birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39211246371269226,
            "question": "Is Zen\u00f3n Franco Ocampos known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34821319580078125,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Paraguay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2986784279346466,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Paraguay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22508059442043304,
            "question": "What are some popular cultural traditions in Paraguay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2110709547996521,
            "question": "What is the capital of Paraguay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17420262098312378,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Paraguay?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Zen\u00f3n Franco Ocampos was born in Paraguay.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8199_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the capital of Paraguay?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8199_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular cultural traditions in Paraguay?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8199_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Paraguay?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8199_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8199_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Zen\u00f3n Franco Ocampos was indeed born in Asunci\u00f3n, Paraguay (on May 12, 1956), which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Zen\u00f3n Franco Ocampos was born in Paraguay.\" Specifically, the documents state \"Zen\u00f3n Franco Ocampos was born in Asunci\u00f3n, Paraguay, on the 12th of May 1956,\" which confirms his birthplace."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}